export const jsQuizz ={
  questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which film was Studio Ghibli’s first official production?",
        choices: [
          "Castle in the Sky",
          "My Neighbor Totoro",
          "Grave of the Fireflies",
          "Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Castle in the Sky"
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which actor from the newest Star Wars trilogy also voiced a protagonist in a Studio Ghibli film?",
        choices: [
          "John Boyega",
          "Lupita Nyong’o",
          "Adam Driver",
          "Daisy Ridley"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Daisy Ridley"
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which Studio Ghibli film was NOT directed by Hayao Miyazaki?",
        choices: [
          "The Wind Rises",
          "Ponyo",
          "Kiki's Delivery Service",
          "Grave of the Fireflies"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer:"Grave of the Fireflies"
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which Studio Ghibli film does NOT include human-like animal characters?",
        choices: [
          "Porco Rosso",
          "Princess Mononoke",
          "From Up on Poppy Hill",
          "Kiki's Delivery Service"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "From Up on Poppy Hill"
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which Studio Ghibli character is featured in the studio’s logo?",
        choices: [
          "Moro from Princess Mononoke",
          "Totoro from My Neighbor Totoro",
          "Calcifer from Howl’s Moving Castle",
          "Jiji from Kiki’s Delivery Service"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Totoro from My Neighbor Totoro"
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which author adapted the movie script for Princess Mononoke?",
        choices: [
          "Michael Chabon",
          "Haruki Murakami",
          "Neil Gaiman",
          "Terry Pratchett"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Neil Gaiman"
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which Studio Ghibli film is based on The Little Mermaid?",
        choices: [
          "Spirited Away",
          "Ponyo",
          "The Tale of Princess Kaguya",
          "Kiki's Delivery Service"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Ponyo"
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which Studio Ghibli film’s protagonist is a World War I veteran?",
        choices: [
          "Seita from Grave of the Fireflies",
          "Porco Rosso from Porco Rosso",
          "Jiro Horikoshi from The Wind Rises",
          "Shun Kazama from From Up on Poppy Hill"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Porco Rosso from Porco Rosso"
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which Studio Ghibli film is based on a Diana Wynne Jones novel?",
        choices: [
          "Only Yesterday",
          "The Cat Returns",
          "Howl’s Moving Castle",
          "The Secret World of Arrietty"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Howl’s Moving Castle"
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: "Which of the following Studio Ghibli films is the director’s original work?",
        choices: [
          "The Secret World of Arrietty",
          "Tales of Earthsea",
          "The Tale of Princess Kaguya",
          "Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "The Tale of Princess Kaguya"
      }
    ]
  
};


export const resultInitialState = {
  score: 0,
  correctAnswers: 0,
  wrongAnswers: 0
}
    